{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Alteration memorandum is prepared by a District Treasury oﬃcer in Form _________",
      "correct_answer": "TA VIII",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " TA 10 ",
        " TA 26",
        "TA IV"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Treasury oﬃcer should keep a register in Form ________ of the pension payment order.",
      "correct_answer": "TR 80",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR 72",
        "TR 56",
        "TR 42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "________ pensioner shall ordinarily appear before the disbursing oﬃcer to claim his pension without preparing a bill.. ",
      "correct_answer": "A leper pensioner",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " A Widow pensioner",
        " A political pensioner",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who is the authority to transfer the payment of pension from any treasury in India to another?",
      "correct_answer": "Accountant General",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Director of Treasuries",
        "Finance Secretary",
        "Head of Department"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "At a pension payable in India remain undrawn for more than ______ year, the pension shall cease to be payable.",
      "correct_answer": "one year",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "two year",
        "six months,
        "three years"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Treasury oﬃcer shall not pay any gratuity except on authority received from ________.",
      "correct_answer": "The accountant General",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Finance department",
        "Head of department",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Treasury savings bank accounts ordered to be closed will not be transferred in Rule",
      "correct_answer": "TSB Rule 33",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TSB Rule 32",
        " TSB Rule 35",
        "TSB Rule 34 "
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Commutation of pensioners with regard to service pensioners is mentioned in which of the following rules?",
      "correct_answer": "R.305 (a)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "R.304",
        "R.303",
        "R.306 (a)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Weekly cash balance report from treasuries should be in Form Number ________",
      "correct_answer": "TR 89",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR 35",
        "TR 42",
        "TR 72"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The currency chests maintained at treasuries contain rupees and notes which belongs to _______",
      "correct_answer": " Reserve Bank of India",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "State Bank of India",
        "ICICI Bank",
        "Govt. of Kerala"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
